anysend.com 2014-12-23

# Send Large Files for FREE. AnySize, AnyFile, AnyWhere | AnySend

[Peter Drucker](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peter_Drucker) a management guru, said once: 'If you can't measure it, you can't manage it'.So, yes! We measure, collect and analyze lots of information to make a great product and the best experience we can. 

  1. What information does AnySend collect and use?   
AnySend gathers information about you, including (but not limited to) information in the following categories: 
    1. Identification data (e.g. name, address, telephone number, mobile number, email address);
    2. Electronic identification data (e.g. IP addresses, cookies, tracking GUID files, crash data);
    3. Banking and payment information (credit card information, account number);
    4. Information about your usage of and interaction with the AnySend software on each PC of yours, including platform, device and connection information, device capability, processing time, UI usage, bandwidth, frame-per-second, statistics on page views, and traffic to and from our websites, browser type, usage statistics and the like; 
    5. Products or services ordered and delivered;
    6. Correspondence between you and AnySend.

  2. How does AnySend use this information? 

The data AnySend collect help us make our products much better for you. For instance, if the product did not connect right, we will analyze all the possible information we know about this issue to fix this in the product. This is all done automatically by our systems without anyone in the middle actually monitor or collect data and use it for his own purposes. 

  3. Linked websites and third party applications 

Although AnySend works with many partners, no one gets access to the data we collected about your experience. The only way your data is disclosed, is when legal authorities issue us a subpoena 

  4. How does AnySend protect your personal information? 

AnySend aims to know as little as possible about you as a person, we are interested more in how our products perform. We take the appropriate organizational and technical measures to protect the personal data and traffic data provided to it or collected by it with due observance of the applicable obligations and exceptions under the relevant legislation. The data can only be accessed by authorized employees of us, subsidiaries or service providers who need to have access to this data in order to be able to fulfill their given duties. 

  5. Contacting You 

AnySend may contact you via email, post mail, SMS, phone or our products and websites to send you messages about tips, faults and service issues. Further, we reserve the right to notify you of any eventual claims related to your use of our software and websites. We may also use the above ways to keep you up to date with news about the AnySend software and services that you have purchased and/or to inform you about other AnySend products or other related information. 

  6. How long is your personal data kept by AnySend? 

AnySend will retain your information for as long as is necessary to: (1) fulfill any of the Purposes we described above or (2) comply with applicable legislation, regulatory requests and relevant orders from competent courts. 

  7. Can this Privacy Policy be modified? 

AnySend will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our software and/or products and customer feedback. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy at AnySend.com/privacy, the "last revised" date will be revised. If there are major changes to this Privacy Policy or in how we will use your personal information, we will notify it by directly sending you a notification. You agree that your continued use of the AnySend software or services after notice shall constitute your acceptance of the Privacy Policy. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of how we collecting, using, and protecting your information. 

  8. How can you contact AnySend? 

To contact AnySend, please submit a support request to customer support via email at [support@anysend.com](mailto:support@anysend.com) All in all, we keep private of the collected information and don't believe in sharing it at all ' why help anyone else compete with us? 

**Beta version**

* AnySend is not just a simple file sender - it is SEND. We strive to accommodate you by always being in a 'learn mode' so whenever you are trying to send, drag, click or find a solution to a problem on the web that we can help with, AnySend will pop automatically with a solution and various offers of different products related to sending such as speed (of sending), backup, storage, protection, printing and so on. 

* None of the data, files, streams that are sent, stored, relayed, transferred or downloaded using AnySend are encrypted. During the current BETA phase and the nature of bugs being bugs, we cannot assure full security or privacy.  
**WARNING** : USER ACCOUNTS WILL BE TERMINATED FOR UNAUTHORIZED UPLOADING OF COPYRIGHT-PROTECTED MATERIAL. 

Users may not access, download or share files uploaded by other users except as expressly permitted in the Terms of Use. AnySend forbids copyright infringement. If you believe that your copyright-protected material has been uploaded to the site, please contact abuse@anysend.com and we will promptly remove the content.
